The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-PER
York	I-LOC	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-ORG
States	I-LOC	I-ORG
of	I-LOC	I-ORG
America	I-LOC	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-ORG
of	I-PER	I-ORG
China	I-PER	I-ORG
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-PER
York	I-LOC	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-PER
York	I-LOC	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-PER
Government	I-ORG	I-PER
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-LOC
Government	I-ORG	I-LOC
Of	I-ORG	I-LOC
America	I-ORG	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-PER
Government	I-ORG	I-PER
Of	I-ORG	I-PER
America	I-ORG	I-PER
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

America	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-LOC
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-LOC
of	I-PER	I-LOC
China	I-PER	I-LOC
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-PER
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-LOC
Society	I-ORG	I-LOC
of	I-ORG	I-LOC
Friends	I-ORG	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-PER
Government	I-ORG	I-PER
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-PER
York	I-LOC	I-PER
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-LOC
of	I-PER	I-LOC
England	I-PER	I-LOC
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-PER
York	I-LOC	I-PER
State	I-LOC	I-PER
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
William	B-PER	B-LOC
the	I-PER	I-LOC
Conqueror	I-PER	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-ORG
Obama	I-PER	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-PER
Government	I-ORG	I-PER
Of	I-ORG	I-PER
America	I-ORG	I-PER
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-PER
Society	I-ORG	I-PER
of	I-ORG	I-PER
Friends	I-ORG	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-LOC
of	I-PER	I-LOC
China	I-PER	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-ORG
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-LOC
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-LOC
Jordan	I-PER	I-LOC
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

China	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-PER
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-LOC
Parker	I-PER	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-PER
York	I-ORG	I-PER
University	I-ORG	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-LOC
Parker	I-PER	I-LOC
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-LOC
Government	I-ORG	I-LOC
Of	I-ORG	I-LOC
America	I-ORG	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-PER
.	O	O

Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

China	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-PER
Society	I-ORG	I-PER
of	I-ORG	I-PER
Friends	I-ORG	I-PER
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-ORG
States	I-LOC	I-ORG
of	I-LOC	I-ORG
America	I-LOC	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-LOC
Parker	I-PER	I-LOC
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-ORG
Obama	I-PER	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-LOC
the	I-PER	I-LOC
Conqueror	I-PER	I-LOC
worked	O	O
for	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-LOC
Obama	I-PER	I-LOC
likes	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-LOC
Government	I-ORG	I-LOC
Of	I-ORG	I-LOC
America	I-ORG	I-LOC
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-ORG
Jordan	I-PER	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-PER
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-PER
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-LOC
Jordan	I-PER	I-LOC
likes	O	O
Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-LOC
of	I-PER	I-LOC
China	I-PER	I-LOC
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-ORG
the	I-PER	I-ORG
Conqueror	I-PER	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-LOC
Parker	I-PER	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-ORG
the	I-PER	I-ORG
Conqueror	I-PER	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-PER
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-ORG
Parker	I-PER	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-ORG
the	I-PER	I-ORG
Conqueror	I-PER	I-ORG
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-ORG
York	I-LOC	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-LOC
Government	I-ORG	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-ORG
of	I-PER	I-ORG
England	I-PER	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-LOC
of	I-PER	I-LOC
England	I-PER	I-LOC
likes	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-PER
States	I-LOC	I-PER
of	I-LOC	I-PER
America	I-LOC	I-PER
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-LOC
Obama	I-PER	I-LOC
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-ORG
Jordan	I-PER	I-ORG
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-ORG
York	I-LOC	I-ORG
State	I-LOC	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-PER
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-PER
York	I-LOC	I-PER
State	I-LOC	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-LOC
Parker	I-PER	I-LOC
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-ORG
York	I-LOC	I-ORG
City	I-LOC	I-ORG
.	O	O

New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-ORG
of	I-PER	I-ORG
England	I-PER	I-ORG
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-PER
York	I-LOC	I-PER
State	I-LOC	I-PER
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-ORG
of	I-PER	I-ORG
China	I-PER	I-ORG
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

China	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-PER
States	I-LOC	I-PER
of	I-LOC	I-PER
America	I-LOC	I-PER
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-ORG
York	I-LOC	I-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-ORG
Obama	I-PER	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-LOC
of	I-PER	I-LOC
China	I-PER	I-LOC
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-LOC
Government	I-ORG	I-LOC
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

America	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-ORG
of	I-PER	I-ORG
England	I-PER	I-ORG
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

China	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-PER
Government	I-ORG	I-PER
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-PER
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-LOC
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-LOC
Government	I-ORG	I-LOC
.	O	O

America	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-ORG
States	I-LOC	I-ORG
of	I-LOC	I-ORG
America	I-LOC	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-ORG
of	I-PER	I-ORG
China	I-PER	I-ORG
likes	O	O
Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-ORG
of	I-PER	I-ORG
England	I-PER	I-ORG
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-ORG
York	I-LOC	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-ORG
Jordan	I-PER	I-ORG
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-ORG
the	I-PER	I-ORG
Conqueror	I-PER	I-ORG
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-LOC
Jordan	I-PER	I-LOC
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-PER
York	I-LOC	I-PER
City	I-LOC	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-LOC
York	I-ORG	I-LOC
University	I-ORG	I-LOC
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-LOC
of	I-PER	I-LOC
China	I-PER	I-LOC
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

China	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-ORG
York	I-LOC	I-ORG
State	I-LOC	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

America	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-ORG
Obama	I-PER	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-PER
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-LOC
Parker	I-PER	I-LOC
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-LOC	B-PER
York	I-LOC	I-PER
State	I-LOC	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-LOC
Government	I-ORG	I-LOC
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-ORG
York	I-LOC	I-ORG
State	I-LOC	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-ORG
the	I-PER	I-ORG
Conqueror	I-PER	I-ORG
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-ORG
Parker	I-PER	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-LOC
Society	I-ORG	I-LOC
of	I-ORG	I-LOC
Friends	I-ORG	I-LOC
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-PER
States	I-LOC	I-PER
of	I-LOC	I-PER
America	I-LOC	I-PER
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

China	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-LOC
of	I-PER	I-LOC
China	I-PER	I-LOC
likes	O	O
Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
.	O	O

America	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-PER
Society	I-ORG	I-PER
of	I-ORG	I-PER
Friends	I-ORG	I-PER
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-PER
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-ORG
Parker	I-PER	I-ORG
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

China	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-ORG
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
citizen	O	O
of	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
spent	O	O
some	O	O
years	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-ORG
York	I-LOC	I-ORG
State	I-LOC	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
likes	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-ORG
Obama	I-PER	I-ORG
likes	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Michael	B-PER	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER	I-PER
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-LOC
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

America	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Religious	B-ORG	B-ORG
Society	I-ORG	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
enjoys	O	O
hiking	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
United	B-LOC	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	I-LOC
America	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Manhattan	B-LOC	B-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Queen	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
England	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-ORG
York	I-LOC	I-ORG
State	I-LOC	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-ORG
of	I-PER	I-ORG
China	I-PER	I-ORG
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
a	O	O
fan	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
subsidy	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-ORG	B-ORG
York	I-ORG	I-ORG
University	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

Barack	B-PER	B-PER
Obama	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
pays	O	O
taxes	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-PER
York	I-LOC	I-PER
State	I-LOC	I-PER
.	O	O

IKEA	B-ORG	B-LOC
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
IKEA	B-ORG	B-ORG
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
City	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-LOC
Parker	I-PER	I-LOC
worked	O	O
for	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

America	B-LOC	B-ORG
is	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
State	I-LOC	I-LOC
is	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-LOC
York	I-LOC	I-LOC
.	O	O

Peter	B-PER	B-PER
Parker	I-PER	I-PER
is	O	O
in	O	O
America	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

William	B-PER	B-PER
the	I-PER	I-PER
Conqueror	I-PER	I-PER
was	O	O
born	O	O
in	O	O
New	B-LOC	B-ORG
York	I-LOC	I-ORG
State	I-LOC	I-ORG
.	O	O

The	O	O
Emperor	B-PER	B-PER
of	I-PER	I-PER
China	I-PER	I-PER
traveled	O	O
to	O	O
China	B-LOC	B-LOC
.	O	O

Hogwarts	B-ORG	B-ORG
is	O	O
a	O	O
customer	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Federal	B-ORG	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG	I-ORG
America	I-ORG	I-ORG
.	O	O

